

HALEY HILTON ZITO

DISTRICT MANAGER

CONTACT

858-945-4569
HALEYMARIEHILTON@GMAIL.COM
WWW.LINKEDIN.COM/IN/HALEYHILTON

EDUCATION

CALIFORNIA STATE UNIVERSITY, NORTHRIDGE
MAY 2014
B.A. COMMUNICATION STUDIES
MINOR PR JOURNALISM

SPECIALIZATIONS

OPERATIONS MANAGEMENT
CUSTOMER EXPERIENCE
REDUCING OPEX
TEAM LEADERSHIP AND PERFORMANCE
MANAGEMENT
MICROSOFT OFFICE
COPY EDITING

REFERENCES

MARY RADOSH

DIRECTOR OF RETAIL | BLENDERS
(309) 333-9378

MARY@BLENDERSEYEWEAR.COM

KALI WEGNER

RETAIL VISUAL MANAGER | MARINE LAYER
(920) 222 - 7640

KALI@MARINELAYER.COM

PROFILE

I have a history of creating and maintaining strong brand messaging while increasing productivity and reducing capital and operating expenditure. I have ten years progressive experience in project management and staff leadership in retail, e-commerce and B2B technology. I have a demonstrated history of working with multiple departments, improving cross-department communication and successfully managing simultaneous projects. I have an entrepreneurial mindset and take initiative in solving day-to-day and global opportunities within the company to ensure longevity and profitability.

EXPERIENCE

DISTRICT MANAGER

MARINE LAYER | APR 2019 - PRESENT

- Increased District profits by 53% in the first year
- Build and maintain diverse, high performing teams; responsible for assessment, training, performance management and ongoing talent development
- Oversee the hiring process and train store leadership team to excel at sourcing, training and retaining top talent
- Drive productivity and profitability across the Retail Channel; responsible for achieving stores' P&L results
- Work closely with Director of Retail and cross-functional partners to develop and execute retail initiatives
- Partner with Brand, Merchandising, Real Estate, and Planning on creating a compelling in-store experience
- Support new store growth and lead execution of new store opening process, year over year comp targets and holding teams accountable for deliverables, customer experience and strategic solution building
- Analyze existing operations and implement strategies, processes and technologies to support company objectives

EXECUTIVE OPERATIONS MANAGER

ALERTMEDIA | APR 2017 - APR 2019

- Managed office operations budget of \$500K, reducing costs by 12% annually
- Executive Admin support to team of 10 including CEO, CFO, CTO, CPO, CRO
- Lead office relocation from 1300 sq ft to 15,000 sq ft.
 Managed all onsite setup and partnered closely with construction managers to ensure closeout of punch lists
- Maintained documents for legal employee files, MNDA, DPA, Vendor Agreements
- Managed all-team communication effort on events, schedule and product release
- Assisted in recruiting and interview processes; lead onboarding of new hires

FRONT OFFICE MANAGER

NIXON | SEP 2016 - FEB 2017

HIRING AND DEVELOPMENT MANAGER

ANTHROPOLOGIE | JAN 2015 - JUNE 2016

STORE MANAGER

MARINE LAYER | SEP 2013 - JAN 2015